Previously on the show.
上集說到
Wolffy used the see-through function of Sirius to catch the goats.
灰太狼用天狼號的透視功能來捉羊
Jonie, who was hiding among the cloud people,
混在小雲人當中的暖羊羊
tried her best to stop Wolffy.
則用盡辦法來阻止灰太狼
In the end,
最終，暖羊羊用嘻哈號的新功能 打敗了灰太狼
What will happen next?
接下來故事將會怎樣發展呢？
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: Where is Wolnie?"
《奇幻天空島之》
Wolnie, today is our anniversary.
紅紅，今天是我們的紀念日
I've got a special gift for you.
我準備了一份貴重的禮物送給妳
Such a big gem! It must be expensive!
這麼大的寶石，一定很貴啊！
Willie, where did you get that gem?
小灰灰，你這是哪來的寶石呢？
From Cloud Giant's home.
在雲巨人家裡呀
There are plenty more very big gems.
那裡還有很多很多、很大很大的寶石
Very big gems?
很大很大的寶石？
Let's go, Wolffy.
灰太狼，走
Where're we going?
去哪？
To get gems!
拿寶石
Jonie, I'm here to take over your shift. Get some rest.
班長，我來接班了，妳快點去休息吧
Thank you.
辛苦你了
I must help as well!
我也要幫忙
We'll split up. I'm sure we can find big gems.
我們兵分兩路，肯定能找到大寶石的
I think I just heard something.
剛才好像聽到什麼聲音了
How could you attack me? I won't let you off just like that!
居然襲擊我，我跟你們沒完
Watch out. Everyone leave this place.
危險，大家快離開這裡啊
Even though I can't find any gems, I'll at least catch you for food.
找不到寶石，也要捉你們回去吃
Help!
救命啊…
My hand?
我的手？
Why have I turned into Jonie?
為什麼我變成了暖羊羊？
Wolnie is too anxious for this. She didn't even plan ahead.
紅紅太心急了，一點計劃都沒有
Such good things never happen to me.
哪會有天上掉餡餅 這種好事在我身上發生呢？
Help me!
快救我呀！
Jonie?
暖羊羊？
So, good things actually happen to me.
原來真有這麼大的餡餅
Here, I'll help you.
我現在來救妳了
I'm not a goat!
我不是羊啊
You are doing well trying to speak like my wife.
學我老婆說話學得挺像的呀
Here's an apple.
來，請妳吃個蘋果
Wait. You're not one of those fake Jonies?
等等，你該不會又是假暖羊羊吧？
Which Jonie is real?
到底哪一隻才是真的呢？
They are looking for Jonie? So you are the real one?
找暖羊羊？所以你是真的了？
Even though I couldn't find any gems, I caught a goat.
雖然找不到寶石，但是捉到羊
Wolnie will be pleased.
相信紅紅一定會高興的
Stop hiding. You can't get away.
別躲了，你是逃不掉的
Did he find me?
難道被發現了？
Everyone is cleaning up.
大家都在大掃除
Don't be lazy.
你就別想偷懶了
By the way, Jonie said she just saw a wolf.
對了，剛才暖羊羊說，看到有狼
You better watch out.
你要小心一點喔
Don't worry, we have Magic Train.
怕什麼？我們有嘻哈號
This room is so big. When will I finish cleaning?
那麼大的房間，清理到什麼時候？
Paddi's the only one left here now. I can catch him too.
現在只剩下懶羊羊了 可以把他也抓了
There's still so much dust. Should we use a vacuum cleaner?
還是這麼多灰塵，要不用吸塵器吧？
Luck is on my side. Even Tibbie is here.
真是天助我也，美羊羊也來了
You guys are helping too? That's great!
你們也要幫忙嗎？太好了
You want to run away?
想逃跑？
Just give up, little goat.
小羊，放棄掙扎吧
I will test out my energy extractor.
看我的能量提取器
Again.
再來
Where is it? Where did it go?
在哪裡啊？怎麼不見了？
How could I leave the energy extractor with Wolnie?
我怎麼可以把能量提取器 放在紅紅那裡呢？
She always leaves things around and loses them immediately.
她總是丟三落四的，一下子就弄丟了
But I don't have to hurry.
不過不著急
I'll think of ways to eat the goat once I get the mark.
我可以先想想得到印記後怎麼吃羊
Should I steam or boil you?
是清蒸呢？還是白灼呢？
My perfume! Wolffy!
我的香水！灰太狼！
Luckily, I'm used to breaking my wife's perfume.
幸好有多年弄壞老婆香水的經驗
That's why my perfumes smell of nothing!
難怪之前的香水沒有香味
Please sign the receipt.
請您簽收一下
So many? Wolnie is spending without thinking again.
這麼多，紅紅又亂花錢了
Return them.
退回去
I'll just tell Wolnie the goods are out of stock.
到時候只要告訴紅紅商家斷貨了
It saves money, and she won't be mad.
那既省錢又不用挨罵了
That's why the clothes I purchased online were all out of stock!
難怪最近要網購的衣服都說缺貨
The food Wolnie prepares is not edible.
紅紅做的這些菜完全吃不下啊
Wolffy! So you were lying when you told me my cooking was great!
灰太狼 原來你平時說的好吃都是騙我的！
I am so hungry. I really want to eat...
好餓呀，好想吃…
No. I must wait for Wolnie.
不行，我要等紅紅回來一起吃
By the way, Jonie said she just saw a wolf.
對了，剛才暖羊羊說看到有狼
You better watch out.
你要小心一點
Did the goats find her?
該不會被小羊們發現了吧？
No, Wolnie!
紅紅不可以有事！
Wolnie, I'm coming to save you.
紅紅，我馬上來救妳
How come there's a bag on the floor?
地上怎麼會有個包？
Please give Wolnie back to me!
你們把紅紅還給我吧
Hand Wolnie over now! Or else I will eat Jonie.
你們快把紅紅交出來 不然的話，我就把暖羊羊吃了
Jonie?
暖羊羊？
Now you're scared, huh?
怎麼樣？怕了吧？
Are you talking about me?
你在說我嗎？
You said you caught Jonie?
你剛才說你捉了班長？
Yes, I caught her!
對，捉的就是他
How come you're here? I locked you up in my house!
你怎麼在這啊？ 我明明把你關在家裡的
I've been here the whole time.
我一直都在這裡啊
Wait, you've been here the whole time? Then where is Wolnie?
等一下，你一直在這裡，那紅紅呢？
I saw Wolnie, but she disappeared immediately.
我見過紅太狼，可是一下子就消失了
Oh, no. Then who's that at home?
糟了，那家裡的那個是誰？
Did the power of my mark turn Wolnie into me?
難道我印記的能力 把紅太狼變成了我？
Will you hurry up and untie me?
還不來幫我解開繩子
Wolnie, it's all my fault!
紅紅，我錯了！
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
怎麼樣？沒受傷吧？
Wolnie, you...
紅紅…你這是…
You did so many things that made me angry,
雖然你做了很多讓我生氣的事情
but when I saw how much you cared about me, I couldn't stay angry.
但是當我看到你這麼緊張我的時候 什麼氣都消了
Wolnie!
紅紅！
This is great.
太好了
Dad, Mom.
爸爸媽媽
How come you're here too?
你們怎麼也在這裡？
Willie, tell Mom.
小灰灰，告訴媽媽
Where are those gems you talked about?
你今天說的那些寶石在哪裡呀？
Over there.
那裡呀
Those gem candies inside are delicious.
裡面的寶石糖果可好吃了
These are the gems you were talking about...
原來你說的是這種寶石
TO BE CONTINUED
（未完待續）